topsecretrecipes.com 2001-10-31

# Privacy Policy

TOP SECRET RECIPES, INC.  
INTERNET SITE PRIVACY POLICY

Top Secret Recipes, Inc. (topsecretrecipes.com) uses its best efforts to respect the privacy of its on-line visitors. Top Secret Recipes may use "cookie" technology only to obtain non-personal information from its on-line visitors in order to improve your on-line experience. For example, we track the total number of visitors to our site in the aggregate. 

Top Secret Recipes only gathers personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, etc. when voluntarily submitted by a visitor.  This information is used solely by Top Secret Recipes or other entities who are involved in the operation of this site for internal purposes and is not sold or transferred to third parties. The only exception to this is while using the Message Boards.  A portion of your IP address will be displayed when posting a message on any of our message boards. Top Secret Recipes reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Be sure to check this page periodically for changes. 

NOTE TO PARENTS ON OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We urge parents to regularly monitor and supervise their children’s on-line activities. 

ADVERTISEMENTS

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. In the course of delivering an ad to you DoubleClick collects certain non-personally identifiable information about your visits to this and other Web sites. This information is used to deliver tailored ads to you. During this process, DoubleClick may also place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. DoubleClick has significant security measures in place in their physical facilities and in their computer systems, databases, and communications networks to strictly protect information contained within their systems from loss, misuse or alteration. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and "opt-out" procedures of DoubleClick, please click [here](http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/).  

Copyright © 2000 Top Secret Recipes, Inc. All Rights Reserved  
Terms and Conditions
